#### Contact

leschebach732@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/leo-eschebach-311448254 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Food Preparation
Baking
Teamwork

Certifications
Driver's License

# Leo Eschebach

Dietary Aide at Aston Park Health Care Center, Fullstack Web Developer

Asheville, North Carolina, United States

## Summary

I am 19 years old and just got out of high school last year. However, I have already taken the initiative to studying within my field of interest both in and out of high school. I have taken AP CS A and AP CS Principles while in school, as well as online CS courses to further boost my knowledge in the field.

## Experience

Aston Park Health Care Center Dietary Aide

Tech Talent South
Web Developer
October 2022 - Present (2 months)
Asheville, North Carolina, United States

Panera Bread Line Cook September 2021 - December 2021 (4 months) North Carolina, United States

### Education

Asheville High School

Computer Science · (September 2021 - June 2022)

Ranney School
Computer Science